Welcome to the Deep Learning Nanodegree program.
欢迎来到深度学习纳米学位课程
I'm Cezanne Camacho, the Curriculum Lead for this program.
我是塞尚 · 卡马乔 这个项目的课程负责人
I'm excited to teach you all about the math and
我很高兴教你们所有的数学知识
programming concepts behind deep learning applications.
深度学习应用背后的编程概念
Deep learning has made many tasks possible,
深度学习使许多任务成为可能,
from language translation and self-driving car navigation,
从语言翻译和自动驾驶汽车导航,
to image and art generation.
形象和艺术的一代
Deep learning is used today to learn from existing data,
深度学习现在被用来学习现有的数据,
notice patterns, and predict future trends.
注意模式 预测未来趋势
It's an active area of research, and at Udacity,
这是一个活跃的研究领域 在 Udacity,
we've developed this program so that you'll learn about some
我们开发了这个程序
of the latest deep learning models and frameworks.
最新的深度学习模型和框架
Deep learning is changing a number of industries.
深度学习正在改变许多行业
No matter what application you're interested in,
不管你对什么应用感兴趣,
being able to program and think critically about
能够编程 能够批判性地思考
deep learning models will be a valuable skill to have.
深度学习模型是很有价值的技能
It's important to always be learning,
学习是很重要的,
and I can't wait to see where this journey takes you.
我迫不及待想看看这趟旅程会把你带向何方 .
最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6